Guide to the Federal Theatre Project photograph collection, 1936-1939
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 1: Production Photographs, 1936-1939; (84 boxes)
  - One-Third of a Nation (New York City, New York), December 1937 - March 1938 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Portland, Oregon), October 1936 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), October 1938 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), October 15 - 31, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), October 15 - 31, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1930s (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), October 31, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Seattle, Washington), May 2, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - One-Third of a Nation (Seattle, Washington), 1930s (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - One-Third of a Nation, 1930s (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - One-Third of a Nation, 1930s (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Othello (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Othello (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Out of the Night (San Diego, California), November 17, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Out of the Night (San Diego, California), November 17, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Out of the Night (San Diego, California), November 17, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Out of the Night (San Diego, California), November 17, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Outside Looking In (Peoria, Illinois), 1937 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Outward Bound (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Outward Bound (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Outward Bound, 1930s (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Palace of Truth (White Plains, New York), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Palace of Truth (White Plains, New York), May 21, 1937 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Parents Wanted (Decatur, Illinois), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Party's Over (Peoria, Illinois), August 1937 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Party's Over (Peoria, Illinois), August 1937 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Party's Over (Peoria, Illinois), August 1937 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Path of Flowers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Path of Flowers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Path of Flowers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Path of Flowers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Patience (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Patience (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Penny Wise (San Diego, California), March 6, 1939 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Penny Wise (San Diego, California), March 6, 1939 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Penny Wise (San Diego, California), March 8, 1939 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - The People's Choice (San Diego, California), July 20, 1937 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - The People's Choice (San Diego, California), July 20, 1937 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - The People's Choice (San Diego, California), July 20, 1937 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - The People's Choice (San Diego, California), July 20, 1937 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Personal Appearance (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Personal Appearance (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Personal Appearance (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Personal Appearance (Cedarhurst, New York), August 24, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Personal Appearance, 1930s (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Personnel, 1930s (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Personnel (Illinois), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Personnel (Illinois), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Personnel (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Personnel (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Personnel -- Living Newspaper Staff (New York), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Personnel -- New York City and Lafayette, 1930s (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Personnel -- Picketing (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Personnel (White Plains, New York), June 16, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Petrified Forest (Miami, Florida), October 16, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Petrouchka (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Petrouchka (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Petticoat Parade (Los Angeles, California), December 18, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Photographs from 1935, Post Road, and others, 1930s (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Actors and Actresses of Federal Theatre, 1930s (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Photographs of Unit 1-B, 1930s (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Photographs of USA Work Program WPA, 1930s (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Pierre Patelin (Oakland, California), April 18 - 28, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Pierre Patelin (Oakland, California), April 28, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Pierre Patelin (New York City, New York), October 20, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Pierre Patelin -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Pierre Patelin (New York City, New York), October 20, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Pinocchio (Los Angeles, California), June 4, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Pinocchio (Los Angeles, California), December 4, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Pinocchio (Los Angeles, California), December 4, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Pinocchio (San Francisco, California), February 9 - 12, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Pinocchio (San Francisco, California), February 9 - 12, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Pinocchio (San Francisco, California), February 9, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Pinocchio (San Francisco, California), February 9 - 12, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Pinocchio (Boston, Massachusetts, Los Angeles, California, and New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Pinocchio (Boston, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Pinocchio (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Pinocchio (New York City, New York), January 6, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Pinocchio (New York City, New York), January 17, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Pinocchio New York production, January 17, 1939
  - Pinocchio (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Pinocchio, 1930s (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Pinocchio, 1930s (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Pioneers of Science -- Radio (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Pirates of Penzance (New York City, New York), May 1937 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Pirates of Penzance (New York City, New York), May 1937 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - The Pizen Song (Jacksonville, Florida), June 24, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Plantation Days (Oakland, California), 1930s (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Plantation Days (Oakland, California), 1930s (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Plantation Days -- Negro (Oakland and San Francisco, California), June 19, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - The Playboy of the Western World (Roslyn, New York), January 12, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - The Playboy of the Western World (Roslyn, New York), January 12, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Pomander Walk (Boston and Salem, Massachusetts), December 22, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Pomander Walk (Boston and Salem, Massachusetts), December 22, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Porgy (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Porgy (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Portable Caravan -- Set Up, 1930s (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Portable Caravan -- Technical, 1930s (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Portable Caravan -- Variety Unit, June 1937 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Portable Theatre (Jacksonville, Florida), February 19, 1938 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Portable Theatre (Jacksonville, Florida), February 19, 1938 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Possession (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Post Road (San Diego, California), October 17, 1938 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Post Road (San Diego, California), October 17, 1938 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Post Road (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Post Road (Denver, Colorado), November 5, 1938 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Post Road (Hempstead, New York), 1930s (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Post Road (Hempstead, New York), July 2, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Post Road (Hempstead, New York), 1930s (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Post Road, 1930s (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Power (San Francisco, California), July 28 - August 19, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Power (San Francisco, California), July 28 - August 19, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Power (San Francisco, California), August 19, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Power (San Francisco, California), August 19, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Power (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Power (New York), 1930s (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Power (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Power (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Power (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Power (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Power (Seattle, Washington), 1930s (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Power, February 1937 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Power, 1930s (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Power, 1930s (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Power, 1930s (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Prelude to Swing (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Prelude to Swing (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), June 15, 1939 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Prelude to Swing (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Prelude to Swing, May 12, 1939 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - The President's Ball, 1930s (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - The President's Ball, 1930s (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Processional (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Processional (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Processional (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Processional (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Processional (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Production in Frame, 1930s (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Production in Frame, 1930s (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Professor Mamlock (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Professor Mamlock (Los Angeles, California), August 16 - 22, 1938 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Professor Mamlock (San Diego, California), 1938 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Professor Mamlock (New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Professor Mamlock (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Professor Mamlock (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Professor Mamlock (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Project Display at Federal Housing Exposition (White Plains, New York), May 14, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Prologue to Glory (Los Angeles, California), June 16, 1938 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Prologue to Glory (Los Angeles, California), June 16 - 19, 1938 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Prologue to Glory (San Francisco, California), May 5 - 6, 1938 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Prologue to Glory (San Francisco, California), May 5 - 6, 1938 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Prologue to Glory (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Prologue to Glory (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Prologue to Glory (San Francisco, California), May 6, 1938 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Prologue to Glory (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Prologue to Glory (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Prologue to Glory (Chicago, Illinois, and New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Prologue to Glory (New Orleans, Louisiana), January 1, 1939 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Prologue to Glory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Prologue to Glory (New York City, New York), May 1939 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Prologue to Glory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Prologue to Glory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Prologue to Glory, 1930s (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Prologue to Glory, 1930s (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Publicity -- Brazilian actors (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Publicity (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Publicity (Oakland, California), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Publicity -- Federal Theatre magazine stills, 1930s (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Publicity (Miami, Florida), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Publicity (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Publicity (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Publicity (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Publicity (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Publicity (Seattle, Washington), 1930s (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Punch and Judy -- Puppet Show, 1930s (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Punch and Judy -- Puppet Show, 1930s (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Puppet Show Cart, 1930s (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - The Purple Door Knob (San Francisco, California), June 22, 1936 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - The Purple Door Knob (San Francisco, California), June 22, 1936 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Purple is as Purple Does (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Purple is as Purple Does (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Purple is as Purple Does (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Purple is as Purple Does (Los Angeles, California), November 24, 1936 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Purple is as Purple Does (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (Los Angeles, California), August 10, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (Los Angeles, California), August 10 - 11, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (San Diego, California), August 21 - September 1, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (San Diego, California), August 31 - September 1, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (San Diego, California), August 31 - September 1, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (San Francisco, California), June 30 - July 6, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (San Francisco, California), June 30 - July 6, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (San Francisco, California), July 1 - 5, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (San Francisco, California), July 1 - 5, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Pursuit of Happiness (Denver, Colorado), December 23, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Pygmalion (Roslyn, New York), July 7, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Pygmalion (Roslyn, New York), July 7, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Pygmalion (Roslyn, New York), July 7, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Pygmalion (Roslyn, New York), July 7, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Pygmalion (Roslyn, New York), July 7, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - The Queen's Husband (San Diego, California), January 12, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - The Queen's Husband (San Diego, California), January 12, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - The Queen's Husband (San Diego, California), January 12, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - The Queen's Husband (San Diego, California), January 12, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Race of Life (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Rachel's Man (Los Angeles, California), June 10, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Rachel's Man (Los Angeles, California), June 10, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Rachel's Man (Los Angeles, California), June 10, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Rachel's Man (San Diego, California), June 10, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Rachel's Man (San Diego, California), April 23, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Rachel's Man (San Deigo, California), April 23, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Rachel's Man (San Deigo, California), April 23, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Rachel's Man (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Rachel's Man (Denver, Colorado), June 26, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Rachel's Man (Des Moines, Iowa), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Rachel's Man (Des Moines, Iowa), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Rachel's Man (Des Moines, Iowa), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Radio -- Jewish Players (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Radio -- Miscellaneous (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Radio -- Radio Almanac (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - New York City Radio Almanac, Radio Unit, circa 1935-1939
    - New York City Radio Almanac, Radio Unit, circa 1935-1939
  - Radio -- Portraits in Oils (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Radio -- Station WHN (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Radio -- Station WOR (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Radio (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Radio (White Plains, New York), May 24, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Radio, 1930s (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Radio Division, 1930s (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Radio -- Project Equipment, 1930s (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Radio -- Project Equipment, 1930s (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Radio -- Evan Roberts and Staff (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Radio Project -- Indian Story -- Almanac Players New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Radio Unit Banquet (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Rain (San Bernardino, California), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Raker, Lorin (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Ready! Aim! Fire! (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Ready! Aim! Fire! (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Ready! Aim! Fire! (Los Angeles, California), October 18, 1937 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Ready! Aim! Fire! (Los Angeles, California), October 18, 1937 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Ready! Aim! Fire! (Los Angeles, California), October 18, 1937 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Ready! Aim! Fire! (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Ready! Aim! Fire! (Tampa, Florida), March 16, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Ready! Aim! Fire!, 1930s (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Rebound (Syracuse, New York), April 2, 1936 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Redemption (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Redemption (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Redemption -- Yiddish (Los Angeles, California), December 23, 1936 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Redemption -- Yiddish (Los Angeles, California), December 23, 1936 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - A Regular Fix (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - A Regular Fix (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - A Regular Fix (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Reich, Molka, 1930s (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Relatives (Los Angeles, California), February 3, 1937 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Relatives (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Remember the Day (Jacksonville, Florida), June 23, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Remember the Day (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Remember the Day (Hempstead, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Remember the Day (Hempstead, New York), March 9, 1936 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Remember the Day (Hempstead, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Return to Death (Boston, Massachusetts), August 18, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Return to Death (Boston, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Revolt of the Beavers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Revolt of the Beavers, New York City, 1937
    - Revolt of the Beavers, New York City, 1937
  - Revolt of the Beavers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Revolt of the Beavers, New York City, 1937
  - Revolt of the Beavers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Revolt of the Beavers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Revue of Reviews (Los Angeles, California), January 13, 1937 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Reward (Tampa, Florida), April 24 - May 1, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Riddle Me This (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Riddle Me This (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Rip Van Winkle -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Rip Van Winkle -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Rip Van Winkle (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Rip Van Winkle -- Marionette (Buffalo, New York), September 25, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Rip Van Winkle -- Marionette (Buffalo, New York), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Rip Van Winkle -- Marionette (Buffalo, New York), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Rip Van Winkle -- Marionette (Roslyn, New York), September 23, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1930s (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1930s (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1930s (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1930s (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Rip Van Winkle, May 13 - 15, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - The Rise of Silas Lapham (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - The Rise of Silas Lapham (Jacksonville, Florida), February 6, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Roadside (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Roadside (Los Angeles, California), April 6, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Roadside (Los Angeles, California), April 6, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Roaring Girl (Los Angeles, California), February 2, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Roaring Girl (Los Angeles, California), February 2, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Robson, William N., 1930s (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Romantic Young Lady (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Romantic Young Lady (San Diego, California), May 12, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Romantic Young Lady (San Diego, California), May 12, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Room Service (San Diego, California), December 28, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Room Service, San Diego, California, December 28, 1938
    - Room Service, San Diego, California, December 28, 1938
  - Room Service (San Diego, California), December 28, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Room Service, San Diego, California, December 28, 1938
    - Room Service, San Diego, California, December 28, 1938
    - Room Service, San Diego, California, December 28, 1938
  - Room Service (San Francisco, California), November 27, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Room Service, San Francisco, California, November 27, 1938
  - Room Service (San Francisco, California), November 27, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Room Service (San Francisco, California), November 27, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Room Service (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Room Service, Denver, Colorado, January 21, 1939
    - Room Service, Denver, Colorado, January 21, 1939
  - Room Service (Denver, Colorado), January 21, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Room Service (Tampa, Florida), January 15, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Room Service (New Orleans, Louisiana), May 11, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Room Service, New Orleans, Louisiana, May 11, 1939
    - Room Service, New Orleans, Louisiana, May 11, 1939
  - Room Service -- Various Productions, 1937 - 1938 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Room Service, May 11, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1930s (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1930s (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1930s (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - The Rose of Picardy (Syracuse, New York), September 3, 1936 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Run, Little Chillun (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Run, Little Chillun (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Run, Little Chillun (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Run, Little Chillun (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Run, Little Chillun (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Run, Little Chillun (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Run, Little Chillun (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Run, Little Chillun (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Run, Little Chillun (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Run, Little Chillun (San Francisco, California), January 11, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 18)